ILR School Librarian's Office Files /4004
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Libraries and Librarians University of Rochester Library, 1946 (Box 14, Folder 11)
- Libraries and Librarians D-5 General, 1949 (Box 14, Folder 12)
- Library Lists Industrial Relations Counselors Inc. Selected Library Accessions List, 1957 (Box 14, Folder 13)
- Library Lists School of Hotel Administration, 1960 (Box 14, Folder 14)
- Library Lists Library References in Industrial Relations, 1957 (Box 14, Folder 15)
- Library Lists Maritime College (N.Y.S.), 1958 (Box 14, Folder 16)
- Library Lists ILR News, 1959 (Box 14, Folder 17)
- Library Lists N.Y.S. Commission Against Discrimination Library Accessions List No. 1, 1954 (Box 14, Folder 18)
- Libraries and Librarians Education, 1948 (Box 14, Folder 19)
- Industrial Relations Librarians Committee Seventh Annual Conference at Toronto, 1953 (Box 14, Folder 20)
- Libraries and Librarians Job Openings, 1949 (Box 14, Folder 21)
- Industrial Relations Librarians Committee - Correspondence Questionnaire, 1948 (Box 14, Folder 22)
- Industrial Relations Librarians Committee - Correspondence (Mildred I. Henry), 1948 (Box 14, Folder 23)
- Industrial Relations Librarians Committee - Correspondence, 1950 (Box 14, Folder 24)
- Industrial Relations Librarians Committee Correspondence, 1949 (Box 14, Folder 25)
- Industrial Relations Librarians Committee Correspondence, 1950 (Box 14, Folder 26)
- Industrial Relations Librarians Committee E-5 Correspondence, 1951 (Box 14, Folder 27)
- Industrial Relations Librarians Committee Correspondence, 1952-1953 (Box 14, Folder 28)
- Industrial Relations Librarians Committee Correspondence, 1954-1955 (Box 14, Folder 29)
- Industrial Relations Librarians Committee 8th Annual Conference at Allerton, Illinois, 1954 (Box 14, Folder 30)
- Industrial Relations Librarians Committee 9th Annual Conference at Ann Arbor, Michigan, 1955 (Box 14, Folder 31)
- Industrial and Labor Relations Committee 11th annual Conference - May 1957 (Box 14, Folder 32)
- Third Annual Conference of Industrial Relations - Librarians, 1949 (Box 14, Folder 33)
- Second Annual Conference of Industrial Relations - Librarians, 1948 (Box 14, Folder 34)
- Special Libraries Association Correspondence, 1947 (Box 14, Folder 35)
- Special Libraries Association General, 1949 (Box 14, Folder 36)
- Special Libraries Association Western New York Chapter, 1949 (Box 14, Folder 37)
- New York Library Association General, 1964 (Box 14, Folder 38)
- American Univ. Field Staff Reports Distribution, 1967 (Box 14, Folder 39)
- General Correspondence "A" Miscellaneous, 1960 (Box 15, Folder 1)
- General Correspondence, 1948 (Box 15, Folder 2)
- General Correspondence, 1949 (Box 15, Folder 3)
- General Correspondence "A" Miscellaneous, 1968 (Box 15, Folder 4)
- General Correspondence Abrahams Magazine Service, 1955 (Box 15, Folder 5)
- General Correspondence Actors' Equity Association, 1963 (Box 15, Folder 6)
- General Correspondence The Ahmedabad Textile Industry's Research Association, 1957 (Box 15, Folder 7)
- General Correspondence Airlines Personnel Relations Conference, 1952 (Box 15, Folder 8)
- General Correspondence National Aniline Division of Allied Chemical and Dye Corporation, 1951 (Box 15, Folder 9)
- General Correspondence Amalgamated Clothing Workers of Amer., 1952 (Box 15, Folder 10)
- General Correspondence American Arbitration Association, 1951 (Box 15, Folder 11)
- General Correspondence American Association of Industrial Eds., 1954 (Box 15, Folder 12)
- General Correspondence American Bar Association, 1954 (Box 15, Folder 13)
- General Correspondence American Booksellers Agency, Inc., 1951 (Box 15, Folder 14)
- General Correspondence American Business, 1950 (Box 15, Folder 15)
- General Correspondence American Civil Liberties Union, 1951 (Box 15, Folder 16)
- General Correspondence American Committee for Cultural Freedom, 1952 (Box 15, Folder 17)
- General Correspondence American Council of Learned Societies, 1954 (Box 15, Folder 18)
- General Correspondence American Cyanamid Company, 1954 (Box 15, Folder 19)
- General Correspondence American Economic Foundation, 1951 (Box 15, Folder 20)
- General Correspondence American Federation of Labor, 1946 (Box 15, Folder 21)
- General Correspondence American Finance Association, 1951 (Box 15, Folder 22)
- General Correspondence American Foundations Information Service, 1954 (Box 15, Folder 23)
- General Correspondence American Hospital Association, 1950 (Box 15, Folder 24)
- General Correspondence American Institute of Management, 1955 (Box 15, Folder 25)
- General Correspondence American Institute of Pacific Relations, Inc., 1950 (Box 15, Folder 26)
- General Correspondence American Iron and Steel Institute, 1953 (Box 15, Folder 27)
- General Correspondence American Jewish Committee, 1952 (Box 15, Folder 28)
- General Correspondence American Legion, 1951 (Box 15, Folder 29)
- General Correspondence American Library Association, 1953 (Box 15, Folder 30)
- General Correspondence american Management Association, 1954 (Box 15, Folder 31)
- General Correspondence american Paper and Pulp Association, 1951 (Box 15, Folder 32)
- General Correspondence American Petroleum Institute (Box 15, Folder 33)
- General Correspondence American Society of Training Directors (Box 15, Folder 34)
- General Correspondence American Society of Training Directors, 1954 (Box 15, Folder 35)
- General Correspondence Arebian American Oil Company, 1959-1960 (Box 15, Folder 36)
- General Correspondence Architectural Forum and House-Home, 1953 (Box 15, Folder 37)
- General Correspondence University of Arizona, 1954 (Box 15, Folder 38)
- General Correspondence The Asia Foundation - California, 1956 (Box 15, Folder 39)
- General Correspondence Arabian American Oil Company, 1959-1960 (Box 15, Folder 40)
- General Correspondence Architectural Forum and House-Home, 1953 (Box 15, Folder 41)
- General Correspondence University of Arizona, 1954 (Box 15, Folder 42)
- General Correspondence University of Arizona, 1954 (Box 15, Folder 43)
- General Correspondence The Asia Foundation - California, 1956 (Box 15, Folder 44)
- General Correspondence Associated Industries of N.Y.S., 1956 (Box 15, Folder 45)
- General Correspondence Associate Press, 1951 (Box 15, Folder 46)
- General Correspondence Association of American Railroads (Miss Helen R. Richardson, Ref. Lib.), 1955 (Box 15, Folder 47)
- General Correspondence Association of Casualty and Surety Cos., 1954 (Box 15, Folder 48)
- General Correspondence Association of Catholic Trade Unionists, 1956 (Box 15, Folder 49)
- General Correspondence Association for Higher Education, 1953 (Box 15, Folder 50)
- General Correspondence The Atlantic Monthly, 1954 (Box 15, Folder 51)
- General Correspondence Atomes Mutual Security Agency, 1953 (Box 15, Folder 52)
- General Correspondence Individual, Atteslander, Peter, 1954 (Box 15, Folder 53)
- General Correspondence The Auburn Citizen-Advertiser, 1952 (Box 15, Folder 54)
- General Correspondence - Individual Aurigemma, Luigi, 1954 (Box 15, Folder 55)
- General Correspondence - Individual Aurigemma, Luigi, 1955 (Box 15, Folder 56)
- General Correspondence Int. Union United Automobile, Aircraft and Agricultural Implement Workers, 1951 (Box 15, Folder 57)
- General Correspondence "B" Miscellaneous, 1960 (Box 15, Folder 58)
- General Correspondence "B' Miscellaneous, 1968 (Box 15, Folder 59)
- General Correspondence Mr. Peter Bachrach (Individual), 1951 (Box 15, Folder 60)
- General Correspondence Baker and Taylor Company, 1957 (Box 15, Folder 61)
- General Correspondence Bankers Trust Company, 1953 (Box 15, Folder 62)
- General Correspondence - Individual Barros, Vincente A. Sota, 1957 (Box 15, Folder 63)
- General Correspondence Individual Barton, Betty, 1950 (Box 15, Folder 64)
- General Correspondence Individual Barton, Betty, 1950 (Box 15, Folder 65)
- General Correspondence Beacon House, Inc., 1950 (Box 15, Folder 66)
- General Correspondence - Individual Behler, Harry, 1955 (Box 15, Folder 67)
- General Correspondence Mathew Bender and Company, 1954 (Box 15, Folder 68)
- General Correspondence Bendix Aviation Corporation, 1952 (Box 15, Folder 69)
- General Correspondence Bernan Associates (Box 15, Folder 70)
- General Correspondence - Individual Beyle, Herman C., 1956 (Box 15, Folder 71)
- General Correspondence Bigelow-Sanford Carpet Co., Inc., 1954 (Box 15, Folder 72)
- General Correspondence The Biometric Society, 1951 (Box 15, Folder 73)
- General Correspondence B. H. Blackwell, Ltd., 1951 (Box 15, Folder 74)
- General Correspondence Individual Emile Bouvier, 1953 (Box 15, Folder 75)
- General Correspondence Individual Mr. Ernest S. Bradford, 1954 (Box 15, Folder 76)
- General Correspondence - Individual Brissenden, Paul F., 1955 (Box 15, Folder 77)
- General Correspondence British Information Service, 1952 (Box 15, Folder 78)
- General Reverence The British Institute of Management, 1952 (Box 15, Folder 79)
- General Correspondence Bro-Dart Industries, 1954 (Box 15, Folder 80)
- General Correspondence Brookings Institution, 1950 (Box 15, Folder 81)
- General Correspondence Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employees, 1957 (Box 15, Folder 82)
- General Correspondence Buffalo Chamber of Commerce, 1953 (Box 15, Folder 83)
- General Correspondence - Individual Burbank, David T., 1957 (Box 15, Folder 84)
- General Correspondence Bureau of Information, 1953 (Box 15, Folder 85)
- General Correspondence Bureau of Information of the Eastern Railways - See Eastern Railroad President's Conference, 1953 (Box 15, Folder 86)
- General Correspondence Bureau of National Affairs, 1954 (Box 15, Folder 87)
- General Correspondence Business Archives Center, Inc., 1952 (Box 15, Folder 88)
- General Reference Business Historical Society, Inc., 1963 (Box 15, Folder 89)
- General Correspondence Business Reports, Inc., 1953 (Box 15, Folder 90)
- General Correspondence Business Screen Magazine, 1954 (Box 15, Folder 91)
- General Correspondence Individual Butler, Harold, 1954 (Box 15, Folder 92)
- General Correspondence "C" Miscellaneous, 1960 (Box 15, Folder 93)
- General Correspondence University of California - Berkeley Institute of Industrial Relations, 1954 (Box 15, Folder 94)
- General Correspondence University of California - Los Angeles Institute of Industrial Relations, 1954 (Box 15, Folder 95)
- General Correspondence California Institute of Technology Industrial Relations Section, 1951 (Box 15, Folder 96)
- General Correspondence Camp Lejeumne, North Carolina, 1955 (Box 15, Folder 97)
- General Correspondence Canada Department of Labour, 1953 (Box 15, Folder 98)
- General Correspondence Capital City News Bureau, Inc., 1954 (Box 15, Folder 99)
- General Correspondence Career, Inc., 1955 (Box 15, Folder 100)
- General Correspondence - Individual Carlson, C. G. Delco-Ramy, 1956 (Box 15, Folder 101)
- General Correspondence Carnegie Endowment for International Peace, 1955 (Box 15, Folder 102)
- General Correspondence Carr Publishing Co. (Box 15, Folder 103)
- General Correspondence Catholic University of America, 1954 (Box 15, Folder 104)
- General Correspondence Central European Federation of Christian Trade Unions, 1956 (Box 15, Folder 105)
- General Correspondence The Century Press, Inc., 1954 (Box 15, Folder 106)
- General Correspondence Individual Albert Chammah, 1954 (Box 15, Folder 107)
- General Correspondence Champlin-Shealy Company, 1954 (Box 15, Folder 108)
- General Correspondence Chandler's, Inc., 1954 (Box 15, Folder 109)
- General Correspondence Channel Master Corp., 1954 (Box 15, Folder 110)
- General Correspondence Chase National Bank, 1953 (Box 15, Folder 111)
- General Correspondence University of Chicago, 1954 (Box 15, Folder 112)
- General Correspondence Chicago University Press, 1953 (Box 15, Folder 113)
- General Correspondence Civil Service Assembly of U.S. and Canada, 1954 (Box 15, Folder 114)
- General Correspondence - Individual Clarke, James E., 1955 (Box 15, Folder 115)
- General Correspondence Coast Guard League, 1957 (Box 15, Folder 116)
- General Correspondence Columbia University, 1954 (Box 15, Folder 117)
- General Correspondence Columbia University Press, 1951 (Box 15, Folder 118)
- General Correspondence Commerce and Industry Assn. of New York, 1953 (Box 15, Folder 119)
- General Correspondence Commerce Clearing House, Inc., 1953 (Box 15, Folder 120)
- General Correspondence Commercial Credit Co., 1954 (Box 15, Folder 121)
- General Correspondence Committee on Diagnostic Reading Tests (Box 15, Folder 122)
- General Correspondence Community Consultant on Services for the Aged, 1950 (Box 15, Folder 123)
- General Correspondence Community Health Association, 1953 (Box 15, Folder 124)
- General Correspondence Community Chests and Councils of America, 1953 (Box 15, Folder 125)
- Congress of Industrial Organization, 1951 (Box 15, Folder 126)
- General Correspondence Congressional Quarterly, 1953 (Box 15, Folder 127)
- General Correspondence University of Connecticut, 1950 (Box 15, Folder 128)
- General Correspondence Contemporary Films, 1954 (Box 15, Folder 129)
- General Correspondence The Controller, 1952 (Box 15, Folder 130)
- General Correspondence Individual Cornsweet, Albert I., 1950 (Box 15, Folder 131)
- General Correspondence Individual Curry, Francis, 1955 (Box 15, Folder 132)
- General Correspondence Coronet Instructional Films, 1951 (Box 15, Folder 133)
- General Correspondence Council of Profit Sharing Industries, 1955 (Box 15, Folder 134)
- General Correspondence Cramer Posture Chair Company, Inc., 1952 (Box 15, Folder 135)
- General Correspondence T.Y. Crowell Publishing Company, 1952 (Box 15, Folder 136)
- General Correspondence "D" Miscellaneous, 1968 (Box 15, Folder 137)
- General Correspondence "D" Miscellaneous, 1960 (Box 15, Folder 138)
- General Correspondence Daily News-Digest, 1952 (Box 15, Folder 139)
- General Correspondence Daily Worker, 1950 (Box 15, Folder 140)
- General Correspondence Dana, William B., Company, 1955 (Box 15, Folder 141)
- General Correspondence - Individual Dandois, R., 1955 (Box 15, Folder 142)
- General Correspondence - Dartnell Corporation, 1954 (Box 15, Folder 143)
- General Correspondence Individual Professor Walter L. Daykin, 1954 (Box 15, Folder 144)
- General Correspondence Daystrom's, 1953 (Box 15, Folder 145)
- General Correspondence Delaware and Hudson Railroad, 1953 (Box 15, Folder 146)
- General Correspondence Dempsey, Jack See Plane Designers, Inc. (Box 15, Folder 147)
- General Correspondence Detroit Labor Trends, 1950 (Box 15, Folder 148)
- General Correspondence Distributors Group, Inc., 1953 (Box 15, Folder 149)
- General Correspondence (Individual) Dr. Joseph H. Diamond, 1951 (Box 15, Folder 150)
- General Correspondence - Individual Donlon, Mary H. (Judge), 1955 (Box 15, Folder 151)
- General Correspondence Doubleday Book Shops, 1954 (Box 15, Folder 152)
- General Correspondence Individual Miss Marie A. Dougherty, 1954 (Box 15, Folder 153)
- General Correspondence Dun's Review and Modern Industry, 1953 (Box 15, Folder 154)
- General Correspondence Individual Joseph T. Dye, 1952 (Box 15, Folder 155)
- General Correspondence "E" Miscellaneous, 1961 (Box 15, Folder 156)
- General Correspondence "E" Miscellaneous, 1960 (Box 15, Folder 157)
- General Correspondence East European Labor Institute, 1953 (Box 15, Folder 158)
- General Correspondence Economic Cooperation Administration, 1951 (Box 15, Folder 159)
- General Correspondence (The) Econometric Society, 1950 (Box 15, Folder 160)
- General Correspondence Economic Statistics Bureau of Washington, D.C., 1950 (Box 15, Folder 161)
- General Correspondence Edinburgh, University of, 1954 (Box 15, Folder 162)
- General Correspondence Editorial Research Reports, 1954 (Box 15, Folder 163)
- General Correspondence Ekholm Associates, 1954 (Box 15, Folder 164)
- General Reference Elliot Service Company, 1953 (Box 15, Folder 165)
- General Correspondence Employers Labor Relations Information Committee, Inc., 1958 (Box 15, Folder 166)
- General Correspondence engineering Index, Inc., 1953 (Box 15, Folder 167)
- General Correspondence Engineering index, 1950 (Box 15, Folder 168)
- General Correspondence Engineers Joint Council, 1956 (Box 15, Folder 169)
- General Correspondence Engineering Societies Library, 1955 (Box 15, Folder 170)
- General Correspondence Individual - Charlotte Erickson, 1951 (Box 15, Folder 171)
- General Correspondence Esso Standard Oil Company, 1954 (Box 15, Folder 172)
- General Correspondence Ethyl Corporation, 1953 (Box 15, Folder 173)
- General Correspondence European Community for Coal and Steel, 1955 (Box 15, Folder 174)
- General Correspondence Executive Books, 1950 (Box 15, Folder 175)
- General Correspondence "F" Miscellaneous, 1959 (Box 15, Folder 176)
- General Correspondence "F" Miscellaneous, 1968 (Box 15, Folder 177)
- General Correspondence Farquhar, F., 1957 (Box 15, Folder 178)
- General Correspondence The Federated Press, 1949 (Box 15, Folder 179)
- General Correspondence Firestone Tire and Rubber Company, 1954 (Box 15, Folder 180)
- General Correspondence University of Florida, 1954 (Box 15, Folder 181)
- General Correspondence Foley's (Mr. L. J. Dewald) (Box 15, Folder 182)
- General Correspondence Footwear News (Box 15, Folder 183)
- General Correspondence Ford Motor Company, 1954 (Box 15, Folder 184)
- General Correspondence Fortune (Miss Jean Cross, 1954 (Box 15, Folder 185)
- General Correspondence The Foundation for Economic Education, 1951 (Box 15, Folder 186)
- General Correspondence Four Continent Book Corporation, 1953 (Box 15, Folder 187)
- General Correspondence Burt Franklin, 1950 (Box 15, Folder 188)
- General Correspondence Fraternal Book Shop, 1950 (Box 15, Folder 189)
- General Correspondence Free Trade Union Committee, 1952 (Box 15, Folder 190)
- General Correspondence Michael Freed, 1955 (Box 15, Folder 191)
- General Correspondence Individual Frost, Theodore, 1950 (Box 15, Folder 192)
- General Correspondence "G" Miscellaneous, 1959 (Box 16, Folder 1)
- General Correspondence "G" Miscellaneous, 1968 (Box 16, Folder 2)
- General Correspondence - Individual Gamma, Victor P., 1955 (Box 16, Folder 3)
- General Correspondence Gaylord Brothers, 1951 (Box 16, Folder 4)
- General Correspondence (Individual) Mr. Walter Geldzahler, 1952 (Box 16, Folder 5)
- General Correspondence General Aniline and Film Corporation, 1956 (Box 16, Folder 6)
- General Correspondence General Bookbinding Company, 1950 (Box 16, Folder 7)
- General Correspondence Aircraft Gas Tribune Division General Electric Company (Box 16, Folder 8)
- General Correspondence General Foods, 1957 (Box 16, Folder 9)
- General Correspondence General Motors, 1954 (Box 16, Folder 10)
- General Correspondence Duff and M. E. Gilfond Book Agency, 1954 (Box 16, Folder 11)
- General Correspondence Graphic Microfilm Corporation, 1954 (Box 16, Folder 12)
- General Correspondence Gray Iron Founder's Society, 1958 (Box 16, Folder 13)
- General Correspondence - Individual Gruen, K. C., 1955 (Box 16, Folder 14)
- General Correspondence "H" Miscellaneous, 1960 (Box 16, Folder 15)
- General Correspondence "H" Miscellaneous, 1968 (Box 16, Folder 16)
- General Correspondence - Individual Hale, Richard W., 1958 (Box 16, Folder 17)
- General Correspondence - Individual Hahn, William H., 1957 (Box 16, Folder 18)
- General Correspondence Hall and McChesney, Inc., 1954 (Box 16, Folder 19)
- General Correspondence Haloid Company, 1951 (Box 16, Folder 20)
- General Correspondence Hanover Bank and Trust Company, 1954 (Box 16, Folder 21)
- General Correspondence Harcourt, Brace and Company, Inc., 1951 (Box 16, Folder 22)
- General Correspondence (Individual) Mrs. J. Bordon Harriman, 1952 (Box 16, Folder 23)
- General Correspondence Harvard Business Review, 1954 (Box 16, Folder 24)
- General Correspondence Harvard University, 1952 (Box 16, Folder 25)
- General Correspondence Harvard University Press, 1950 (Box 16, Folder 26)
- General Correspondence Haverford College, 1952 (Box 16, Folder 27)
- General Correspondence University of Hawaii, 1952 (Box 16, Folder 28)
- General Correspondence Health Information Foundation, 1957 (Box 16, Folder 29)
- General Correspondence Health Insurance Plan, 1955 (Box 16, Folder 30)
- General Correspondence Individual Miss Mildred Henry, 1953 (Box 16, Folder 31)
- General Correspondence Hershey Chocolate Corp., 1954 (Box 16, Folder 32)
- General Correspondence, 1948 (Box 16, Folder 33)
- General Correspondence Individual - Hill, Edward, 1954 (Box 16, Folder 34)
- General Correspondence - Individual Hillman, Sydney, 1955 (Box 16, Folder 35)
- General Correspondence Hirsch and Company, 1954 (Box 16, Folder 36)
- General Correspondence (Individual) Mr. Aaron Horvitz, 1952 (Box 16, Folder 37)
- General Correspondence Household Finance, 1954 (Box 16, Folder 38)
- General Correspondence Individual Herbert Hubben, 1954 (Box 16, Folder 39)
- General Correspondence Hudgens, Lucia T. (Miss) (Box 16, Folder 40)
- General Correspondence "I" Miscellaneous, 1960 (Box 16, Folder 41)
- General Correspondence Ideal Pictures, 1954 (Box 16, Folder 42)
- General Correspondence University of Illinois, 1954 (Box 16, Folder 43)
- General Correspondence Industrial Hygiene Foundation, 1953 (Box 16, Folder 44)
- General Correspondence Industrial Psychology, Inc., 1954 (Box 16, Folder 45)
- General Correspondence Industrial Psychology (Box 16, Folder 46)
- General Correspondence Industrial Relations Counselors, Inc., 1951 (Box 16, Folder 47)
- General Correspondence Industrial Relations Research Association, 1954 (Box 16, Folder 48)
- General Correspondence Inland Steel Corporation, 1954 (Box 16, Folder 49)
- General Correspondence Institute of Life Insurance, 1952 (Box 16, Folder 50)
- General Correspondence Institute of Mathematical Statistics, 1950 (Box 16, Folder 51)
- General Correspondence The Institute of Public Affairs, 1951 (Box 16, Folder 52)
- General Correspondence Institute of Social Order, 1953 (Box 16, Folder 53)
- General Correspondence International Association of Personnel in Employment Security (Box 16, Folder 54)
- General Correspondence International Film Bureau, Inc., 1953 (Box 16, Folder 55)
- General Correspondence International Free Trades Union Committee, 1950 (Box 16, Folder 56)
- General Correspondence International Labor Directory, 1950 (Box 16, Folder 57)
- General Correspondence International Labor Office (Washington Branch), 1958 (Box 16, Folder 58)
- General Correspondence International Ladies Garment Workers Union, 1953 (Box 16, Folder 59)
- General Correspondence International Landworkers' Federation, 1951 (Box 16, Folder 60)
- General Correspondence University of Iowa, 1954 (Box 16, Folder 61)
- General Correspondence Ithaca Ice Cream Co., 1954 (Box 16, Folder 62)
- General Correspondence Ithaca Journal, 1952 (Box 16, Folder 63)
- General Correspondence "I" Miscellaneous, 1961 (Box 16, Folder 64)
- General Correspondence Ithaca Textile Inc., 1959 (Box 16, Folder 65)
- General Correspondence "J" Miscellaneous, 1968 (Box 16, Folder 66)
- General Correspondence "J" Miscellaneous, 1960 (Box 16, Folder 67)
- General Correspondence Jefferson School of Social Science, 1950 (Box 16, Folder 68)
- General Correspondence The Jewish Hospital of Brooklyn, 1954 (Box 16, Folder 69)
- General Correspondence John Hopkins University, 1953 (Box 16, Folder 70)
- General Correspondence Johnson and Johnson, 1953 (Box 16, Folder 71)
- General Correspondence "K" Miscellaneous, 1968 (Box 16, Folder 72)
- General Correspondence "K" Miscellaneous, 1960 (Box 16, Folder 73)
- General Correspondence Individual Kasper, Harold, 1950 (Box 16, Folder 74)
- General Correspondence Kelly-Read and Company, Inc., 1950 (Box 16, Folder 75)
- General Correspondence Individual Kolaja, Jiri, 1954 (Box 16, Folder 76)
- General Correspondence Leon Kramer, Bookseller, 1954 (Box 16, Folder 77)